meetcleo.com 2017-02-21

# Cleo - Privacy

Your trust is a top priority to us and as such we take privacy extremely seriously. This policy applies to the entire Cleo AI ecosystem. If you do not accept this policy, you may not use the service. 

### Personal Information

We collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) when you fill in registration forms, submit comments to the Site, or send emails to us. Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

### Use of Your Information

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services and developing our business which includes (without limitation):

  * Personalising your visits to the Site to improve the services provided to you.
  * Informing you about the latest changes to the Site, products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting.
  * To notify you about changes to the Service.
  * Communicating (and personalising such communication) with you.
  * Enabling you to share our content with others e.g. using an ‘Email a friend’ or ‘Share this’ functionality.
  * Conducting market research.
  * Carrying out technical and statistical analysis to measure the performance of our services and the Site.

If you cancel your user account for the Service, we will promptly and securely delete all of the Personal Information we hold about you. However, we reserve the right to retain any Anonymous Data collected up to the point of cancellation and to continue using it in accordance with this policy.

### Sharing Your Information

We may share information about you with suppliers that we engage to help us provide certain services and/or functionality e.g online payment processing. We will use reasonable endeavours to control and be responsible for the use of your information by such suppliers. Furthermore, by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (which may not provide the same protection for such information as the European Economic Area provides) in the event that the processing of your information involves such a transfer.

### Keeping Your Personal Information Secure

We take the security of your personal information very seriously and have appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures in place to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure as required by law in England. Once we have received your User Information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access including: 

  * by encrypting any Personal Information which we transfer to SaltEdge Inc; and
  * having in place an agreement with SaltEdge Inc which requires it to have in place appropriate measures to safeguard the security of the Personal Information we send to them. 

Full information on SaltEdge's security policy can be found at <https://www.saltedge.com/pages/bank_level_security>

### Accessing Your Personal Information

If you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hold about you, change your marketing preferences or have any other privacy queries, please write to us (including full details of your request) at the following email address: team@meetcleo.com. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the Personal Information we hold about you. 

### Changes To This Policy

If we change this policy, we will post the revised policy here with an updated effective date. If we make significant changes to the policy, we may also notify you by other means such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page. 

### Cookies Policy

In addition to personal information you provide, we may also collect information about you automatically when you visit the Site or access content in our electronic communications with you. The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor traffic on the Site or within electronic communications. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by your browser. Cookies allow us to identify your computer and find out details about your visit and browsing habits so that we can offer you a more personalised experience and manage, monitor and improve services. You can learn more about cookies and how to reject cookies using different types of browser by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org.
